{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Which of the answers listed below refers to a mobile device's built-in functionality enabling the usage of locator applications?",
      "options": ["WPS", "GSM", "SIM", "GPS"],
      "correct_answers": ["GPS"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following answers refers to a unique 48-bit address assigned to every network adapter?",
      "options": ["PIN", "SSID", "IP", "MAC"],
      "correct_answers": ["MAC"]
    },
    {
      "question": "In older, non-UEFI based PCs, the first sector of a storage drive containing information about partitions and a piece of executable code used to load the installed OS is called:",
      "options": ["MBR", "GPT", "PXE", "GUID"],
      "correct_answers": ["MBR"]
    },
    {
      "question": "In cloud computing, users on an on-premises network take advantage of a transit gateway to connect to:",
      "options": ["WAN", "VPC", "SAN", "VLAN"],
      "correct_answers": ["VPC"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the answers listed below refer to DSA? (Select 3 answers)",
      "options": [
        "Asymmetric algorithm",
        "Used for the key exchange process",
        "Symmetric algorithm",
        "Provides authentication, integrity, and non-repudiation",
        "Specifically designed for creating and verifying digital signatures",
        "Used for encryption"
      ],
      "correct_answers": [
        "Asymmetric algorithm",
        "Provides authentication, integrity, and non-repudiation",
        "Specifically designed for creating and verifying digital signatures"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following acronyms refer to office equipment that combines the functionality of multiple devices? (Select 2 answers)",
      "options": ["MFD", "IoT", "MFP", "PED", "MFA"],
      "correct_answers": ["MFD", "MFP"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the answers listed below describe(s) the characteristics of ECDSA? (Select all that apply)",
      "options": [
        "Provides authentication, integrity, and non-repudiation",
        "Based on elliptic curve cryptography",
        "Designed for data encryption",
        "Specifically designed for creating and verifying digital signatures",
        "More computationally efficient than other signature algorithms",
        "Enables the key exchange process"
      ],
      "correct_answers": [
        "Provides authentication, integrity, and non-repudiation",
        "Based on elliptic curve cryptography",
        "Specifically designed for creating and verifying digital signatures",
        "More computationally efficient than other signature algorithms"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following answers refers to a deprecated stream cipher used in some legacy applications, such as WEP?",
      "options": ["RSA", "DES", "SSL", "RC4"],
      "correct_answers": ["RC4"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the answers listed below refers to a wireless network authentication protocol that enhances security by encapsulating the authentication process within an encrypted TLS tunnel?",
      "options": ["PEAP", "EAP", "LEAP", "RADIUS"],
      "correct_answers": ["PEAP"]
    },
    {
      "question": "A type of metric used to evaluate the profitability of an investment by comparing the return generated from the investment relative to its cost is referred to as:",
      "options": ["ROA", "ROI", "ROS", "ROC"],
      "correct_answers": ["ROI"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following facilitates the enforcement of mobile device policies and procedures?",
      "options": ["MFA", "MMC", "MDM", "MFD"],
      "correct_answers": ["MDM"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the answers listed below refers to an identifier used for objects in a PKI, such as CAs, digital certificates, and public key algorithms?",
      "options": ["OID", "DN", "SAN", "GUID"],
      "correct_answers": ["OID"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following answers refers to a solution designed to strengthen the security of session keys?",
      "options": ["ECB", "PFS", "EFS", "PFX"],
      "correct_answers": ["PFS"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the answers listed below refers to a twisted-pair copper cabling type not surrounded by any shielding that would provide protection against interference from outside sources?",
      "options": ["STP", "Coax", "UTP", "Twinax"],
      "correct_answers": ["UTP"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following terms refers to a technology that enables real-time audio and video communication between individuals or groups?",
      "options": ["VPC", "VTC", "VoIP", "VDI"],
      "correct_answers": ["VTC"]
    },
    {
      "question": "A dedicated data storage solution that combines multiple disk drive components into a single logical unit to increase volume size, performance, or reliability is known as:",
      "options": ["SAN", "RAID", "NAS", "JBOD"],
      "correct_answers": ["RAID"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the answers listed below can be used to describe XSRF? (Select 3 answers)",
      "options": [
        "Exploits the trust a website has in the user's web browser",
        "A user is tricked by an attacker into submitting unauthorized web requests",
        "Website executes attacker's requests",
        "Exploits the trust a user's web browser has in a website",
        "A malicious script is injected into a trusted website",
        "User's browser executes attacker's script"
      ],
      "correct_answers": [
        "Exploits the trust a website has in the user's web browser",
        "A user is tricked by an attacker into submitting unauthorized web requests",
        "Website executes attacker's requests"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following answers can be used to describe the characteristics of an XSS attack? (Select 3 answers)",
      "options": [
        "Exploits the trust a user's web browser has in a website",
        "A malicious script is injected into a trusted website",
        "User's browser executes attacker's script",
        "Exploits the trust a website has in the user's web browser",
        "A user is tricked by an attacker into submitting unauthorized web requests",
        "Website executes attacker's requests"
      ],
      "correct_answers": [
        "Exploits the trust a user's web browser has in a website",
        "A malicious script is injected into a trusted website",
        "User's browser executes attacker's script"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the answers listed below refers to an encoding method (and a file format) for storing cryptographic objects such as X.509 certificates, CRLs, and private keys?",
      "options": ["ECB", "PEM", "FIM", "PFS"],
      "correct_answers": ["PEM"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following answers refers to a centralized server that is used to distribute cryptographic keys and authenticate users and services within a computer network?",
      "options": ["PKI", "RAS", "KDC", "NAS"],
      "correct_answers": ["KDC"]
    },
    {
      "question": "An AI feature that enables it to accomplish tasks based on training data without explicit human instructions is called:",
      "options": ["AGI", "ML", "NN", "LLM"],
      "correct_answers": ["ML"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which data packet type is specifically used to detect and prevent network loops in Ethernet networks?",
      "options": ["MTU", "Jumbo frame", "BPDU", "Magic packet"],
      "correct_answers": ["BPDU"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the answers listed below refers to a key exchange protocol that generates temporary keys for each session, providing forward secrecy to protect past and future communications?",
      "options": ["PFS", "SHA", "PGP", "DHE"],
      "correct_answers": ["DHE"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following terms refers to a method for managing infrastructure resources through scripts and templates?",
      "options": ["IaaS", "ML", "IaC", "SDN"],
      "correct_answers": ["IaC"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the answers listed below refer to the characteristic features of NIDS? (Select 3 answers)",
      "options": [
        "Takes proactive measures to block or mitigate intrusion attempts",
        "Does not take direct action to block or prevent attacks",
        "Generates alerts and notifies security personnel or administrators when suspicious activity is detected",
        "Monitors network traffic without direct involvement in traffic routing or packet modification",
        "Can drop or reject network packets, terminate connections, or take other actions to stop the attack",
        "Operates in an inline mode, actively intercepting and inspecting network traffic"
      ],
      "correct_answers": [
        "Does not take direct action to block or prevent attacks",
        "Generates alerts and notifies security personnel or administrators when suspicious activity is detected",
        "Monitors network traffic without direct involvement in traffic routing or packet modification"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following answers refers to a cybersecurity framework that combines network and security functions into a single cloud-based service?",
      "options": ["SASE", "SIEM", "SWG", "SOAR"],
      "correct_answers": ["SASE"]
    },
    {
      "question": "A process used by organizations to assess and evaluate the potential impact of disruptive incidents or disasters on their critical business functions and operations is referred to as:",
      "options": ["BPA", "BIA", "SLE", "BCP"],
      "correct_answers": ["BIA"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the answers listed below refers to one of the last stages in SDLC?",
      "options": ["UCD", "QA", "UAT", "AUT"],
      "correct_answers": ["UAT"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which cipher mode transforms a block cipher into a stream cipher enabling the encryption of individual bits or bytes of data?",
      "options": ["CFB", "CBC", "GCM", "ECB"],
      "correct_answers": ["CFB"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Rewriting the destination IP address of incoming data packets, commonly utilized to reroute traffic to alternative locations or ports is a characteristic feature of:",
      "options": ["IDS", "DNAT", "QoS", "VPN"],
      "correct_answers": ["DNAT"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following answers refers to a deprecated encryption protocol?",
      "options": ["SSH", "SHA-256", "S/MIME", "SSL"],
      "correct_answers": ["SSL"]
    },
    {
      "question": "A collection of precompiled functions designed to be used by more than one Microsoft Windows application simultaneously to save system resources is known as:",
      "options": ["DLL", "API", "INI", "EXE"],
      "correct_answers": ["DLL"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the terms listed below refers to a documented plan outlining the steps that should be taken in each phase of a cybersecurity incident?",
      "options": ["DRP", "IRP", "BCP", "ERP"],
      "correct_answers": ["IRP"]
    },
    {
      "question": "A block cipher mode that combines a unique counter with encryption key to generate a stream of pseudorandom data blocks which are then used for encrypting data is called:",
      "options": ["CBC", "GCM", "CFB", "CTM"],
      "correct_answers": ["CTM"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following combines a cryptographic hash function with a secret key to provide a means of verifying both the authenticity and integrity of a message or data?",
      "options": ["MD5", "DSA", "HMAC", "DES"],
      "correct_answers": ["HMAC"]
    }
  ]
}